- Oh. Buongiorno.
- Sorry?
（意语）早安
－什么？
－（意语）早安
- Buongiorno.
- Oh, yeah.
Uh, buongiorno.
（意语）早安
Honey.
My arm's asleep.
宝贝
我的手臂麻了
Ethan?
伊森？
Honey?
You all right?
你还好吗？
Yeah, I'm fine.
没事
帕吉欧，你的岗位在外面
亚珊卓，不准喝咖啡
早安，瓦伦蒂娜
Buongiorno.
罗可，还摸鱼？
所有人快点去工作
＂柜台＂
Oh, God.
This is such a beautiful view.
天啊
景色真美
I wonder if anyone's
ever jumped from here.
不知有没有人从这里跳下去过
I'm gonna get a plate.
我去拿盘子
No idea why I didn't
bring my roller skates.
我竟然没带滑轮鞋
- Hey.
- Hi.
Uh, can I sit here?
可以坐这里吗？
Yeah. Yeah, sure, of course.
Or there.
当然可以
你坐吧
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
Yeah, I'm just, um...
It's... My boss is just...
很好，只是‥
我的老板‥
Shoot.
可恶
Well, good thing
it wasn't glass.
还好不是玻璃的
Yeah.
是啊
I only have four hands.
我手不够用
I think they're gonna come
and help you.
他们应该会来帮你
- Hi. No worries.
- Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
我很抱歉，我‥
I just... Do you have
any Oreo cookie cake?
你们有奥利奥蛋糕吗？
Have you noticed that?
Is that cheese, or...
- This is cheese.
- Harper!
哈珀
Hey!
- It's all right.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Where's your man?
你的男人在哪里？
Oh, he wakes up
super early to go running,
他很早就起床去跑步了
so that's what I'm dealing with.
他就是这样
What? Christ, I hate him.
什么？
天啊，我讨厌他
- Got to exercise, you know?
- Dad! Over here.
运动很重要
爸，这里
I still don't have my clothes.
Call the airline.
Morning.
早安
- This is my dad, Dominic.
- Hi.
这位是我爸多米尼克
你好
Nonno, you met Portia yesterday.
爷爷，你昨天见过波蒂亚了
Hi.
Did I?
是吗？
Yeah, I, uh,
saw you fall by the pool.
是的，我看到你在泳池边跌倒
They need
to fill in that grouting.
他们应该把瓷砖缝补好
This is a five-star hotel
这里可是五星级的饭店
这是很严重的安全隐患
and that's a major hazard.
Can we get some menus
and coffee?
可以给我们菜单和咖啡吗？
Did you not sleep well?
你们没睡好吗？
I slept like crap.
我睡得很差
我睡得很好
I slept fantastic
and I'm completely refreshed.
Uh, no jet lag at all.
精力充沛
已经感觉不到时差了
Well, Albie told me
you guys are here to learn
阿尔比说你们是来西西里寻根的
- about your Sicilian roots.
- Uh-huh.
Sounds like a fun boys' trip.
这趟男人的旅行感觉不赖
Well, wasn't
supposed to be a boys' trip.
不该只有男人来的
I still don't understand
why Abby isn't here.
我还是不懂为何艾比不来
I definitely explained it
to you.
我已经跟你解释过了
She's that mad
that she's gonna miss
她气到连一生一次的
西西里家族旅行都不来？
a once-in-a-lifetime family trip
to Sicily?
She is that mad,
and can we just not?
她就是这么气，可以不要说了吗？
What?
怎么了？
She's gonna get a divorce?
She can't do that.
她又不能离婚
Yes, she can.
Why can't she?
她可以，为什么不行？
Um. Well, what's it been?
Twenty-five years?
已经２５年了吧？
I mean...
You can't let her do that.
你不能让她离婚
It's not all up to me, Dad.
这不是我能决定的，爸爸
You want me to call her? Huh?
要我打给她吗？
I'll talk to her.
I can speak to this.
我会跟她聊聊
讨论这件事
I don't want you to call her
我不希望你打给她，这不会有帮助
and that's not gonna help
anything, so...
please can we just drop it?
所以可以不要再说了吗？
My wife passed away last year.
我妻子去年去世了
- Oh, no.
- Yeah.
真不幸
Well, she was very sick, so...
她病得很重‥
We were married 53 years.
The love of my life.
我们结婚５３年了，她是我的挚爱
Dominic's mother.
An incredible woman.
多米尼克的母亲
很棒的女人
And there's no way
她绝对不可能‥
she would've missed
a family trip to Sicily.
错过来西西里的家族旅行
I mean,
I could've done anything.
无论我做了什么事
I could have burned
the house down.
我把房子烧了她都会来
You know what? I think
maybe I will do the buffet.
我还是去自助吧拿吃的好了
You kidding me?
This is bullshit.
你在开玩笑吗？
这根本是在胡扯
No, I filled out
your fucking form.
不对，我明明填了表单
I talked to like three people,
and after all that,
跟三个人谈过
结果你们寄回纽约了？
you send it back
to fucking New York?
Cameron has a really long fuse.
But then all of a sudden,
卡麦隆脾气很好
但一生气就会失控
he'll just go crazy.
I mean, he will lose it.
会完全失去理智
- No. No, no, no, no.
- It's kinda funny.
－不对‥
－还挺好笑的
No.
I don't want a voucher!
我不要优惠券
I want my fucking clothes!
我就是要我的衣服
Does he ever lose it on you?
他会对你暴怒吗？
No. We never fight.
不会
我们从来不会吵架
- That's sweet.
- Yeah.
－真好
－是啊
I don't think I've ever met
a couple that doesn't fight.
我应该没见过不会吵架的情侣
I mean, what is there
to fight about anyway, right?
又没什么事情可以吵，对吧？
Wow.
What'd they say?
他们怎么说？
They sent my bag
back home to New York.
他们那些天才
把我的行李寄回纽约了
- Fucking geniuses.
- No.
Okay, well,
at least it's not lost.
好吧，至少不是丢失了
We'll get you some new stuff.
It'll be great.
我们去买新的，会很棒的
Incompetence,
makes me homicidal.
真没用，让我想杀人
Hmm.
I was just telling Harper
我刚才跟她说我们从不吵架
how we never fight.
Well, you're practically
perfect, so...
你已经近乎完美了，所以‥
And when we disagree,
you just give in, right?
如果我们有争执，你会让我吧？
Yes, ma'am.
没错，女士
Happy wife, happy life.
老婆开心，生活才会开心
I'm gonna, uh, take this up...
我要拿去房间吃
Back up to my room.
Well, we're
kinda done here, right?
我们也差不多吃完了
是啊，我们可以跟你上去
Yeah, we can come with you.
- Great.
- Cool.
－太好了
－好
Oh, yes.
Mm.
It's our first day in Sicily.
What do you wanna do?
这是我们在西西里的第一天
你想做什么？
Whatever you want.
你想做什么都行
I think...
my fantasy day in Italy is...
我的意大利梦幻一日行程
Well, first, I wanna look
just like Monica Vitti.
首先，我要打扮得像莫妮卡维蒂
And... and then this man
in a very slim-fitting suit...
接着有位穿着修身西装的男人
he comes over
and he lights my cigarette.
过来帮我点烟
And it taste really good.
香烟的味道非常棒
And then takes me for a drive
on his Vespa.
然后他会骑伟士牌载我去兜风
You want me to rent a Vespa?
你要我去租一辆伟士牌？
Then at sunset...
黄昏时
we go down
very close to the sea,
我们会去海边，那种很浪漫的地方
to one of those
really romantic spots.
And then we...
we drink lots of aperitivos,
吃饭前会喝很多开胃酒
and we eat big plates of pasta
with giant clams.
然后吃很大盘的意大利面
还有很大的蛤蜊
And we're just really chic
and happy and... and we're...
我们会很高雅，也很开心
我们会‥
beautiful.
很美丽
Well, all right.
Sounds good to me.
好，我觉得不错
Really?
真的吗？
Sure. Whatever you want.
It's... it's your day to shine.
当然，你想做什么都好
今天你是主角
So, your employer
doesn't want you around, huh?
你的雇主不希望你在身边？
Listen. You can't come to Sicily
and just sit in your room.
来西西里不能只待在房里
It's against the law.
这是不能接受的
I know. I agree. It sucks.
我知道，我也同意
这样太糟了
We're walking
to the Greek theater today.
我们今天要步行去希腊剧场
You should come.
你应该一起来
No. It's a family trip,
it's your thing.
不行，我不该打扰你们的家族旅行
Not at all. When there's
a young, pretty lady around,
没关系
有位年轻美丽的女士陪同
we'll all be better behaved,
cheerier.
我们会比较安分
－比较欢乐
－够了
Okay. Yes, no. You...
You should come.
对，你应该一起来
- Right?
- Yeah. Yeah, absolutely.
－对吧？
－对
当然
Hmm? Say yes.
一起来吧
Yes. I'll come.
好
我会去
All right, well we're gonna go
get him some clothes,
我们要去帮他买些衣服
but you wanna meet up
in like two hours?
要不要两小时后见？
Yeah, perfect. Just text us.
好，再传讯息给我们
- Bye.
再见‥
I can't believe how hot...
Hey. What's going on?
怎么了？
What's with the boner?
你怎么勃起了？
Yeah, fair question.
问得好
Uh, I was jerking off.
我在自慰
Oh.
Why?
为什么？
Um, I don't know, endorphins?
不知道，是脑内啡吧
You know I sometimes get horny
after I run.
你知道我有时跑完步会兴奋
Well, couldn't you
have just waited
你不能等到我回来吗？
till I got back to the room?
I was only gone 15 minutes.
我只离开了十五分钟
只吃了一个可颂
All I had was a croissant.
You don't like morning sex.
你不喜欢在早上做
What? I'm fine with it.
我可以啊
Are you?
You're not a morning person.
真的吗？
你早上状态不好
Well, I don't wake up
with a raging hard-on,
我醒来时不会勃起
that is true.
这点的确是真的
Look, I just figured
I'd take care of it myself.
我只是想自己处理掉，好吗？
Okay?
- Well, did you?
- No, but... but it's fine.
那你处理完了吗？
没有，但是‥
没关系
Do you want help?
你需要帮助吗？
现在吗？
Now?
Yeah.
－对
－不用了，没关系
No, it... It's okay.
We can do that later.
晚点再说，没什么
It's not a big deal.
So, Daphne and Cameron
never fight!
达芙妮和卡麦隆从来不吵架
- How do you know?
- Because that's what they said.
－你怎么知道？
－他们是这样说的
不吵架就只是在欺骗彼此
If you never fight,
then your relationship
is not real. It's like, yeah,
我们的确会吵架
we fight, we bicker,
but that's because we talk
about everything.
但那是因为我们无所不谈
You know? We're honest.
我们对彼此诚实
They act like they're
on their honeymoon.
他们表现得像在蜜月期，甜甜蜜蜜
They're all over each other.
But it's bogus. It's not real.
但全都是假的
都是骗人的
You always do this
with certain people.
你对某些人都会这样
It's like you have to find them
deficient in some way,
非要找到对方的缺点
显得你比较优秀
- compared to you.
- What?
什么？
It's like, I don't know,
或许这是你在感到威胁时
安慰自己的方式
maybe it's a way of soothing
yourself
when you feel threatened
or something.
I'm not threatened by them.
我才没有被他们威胁到
Like, you never do this
with Carmen.
你对卡门就不会这样
- Carmen? Our housekeeper?
- You're always like...
你是说我们的女管家？
你总是说＂我好喜欢卡门，她真好＂
"Oh, my God.
I love Carmen. She's so sweet."
She is so sweet.
She's a sweet old lady.
她的确是很友善的老太太
But like,
you're not threatened by her,
她不会让你感到威胁
so you don't see any
of the other stuff.
所以你看不到其他地方
Like, she can just be
sweet Carmen,
她就只是个友善的老太太
the sweet old lady.
Everybody compares themselves
to other people, Ethan.
大家都会跟别人比较，伊森
Why are you criticizing me
for doing something
为何要指责我做大家都会做的事？
that everyone does?
I'm just pointing out
a personality quirk.
我只是在说你性格奇怪的地方
You do it to me all the time.
你也都会这样对我
Why are you threatened by them?
他们为什么让你感到威胁？
- I'm not.
- Kinda seems like you are.
没有这回事
看起来有
But it's just, like,
are these the kind of people
我们现在都要跟那种人相处了吗？
we're gonna be hanging out
with now? Like, really?
那些只会聊曾住过哪间五星饭店的人
Like, people
that can only talk about
what five-star hotel
they've stayed at.
所以你是个势利鬼吗？
Okay, so you're a snob?
What? I'm a snob? They're snobs.
我是势利鬼？
他们才是
I... I guess we're all snobs
in different ways.
每个人在某种程度上应该都是
I was just trying to say
我只是想说我们的关系很棒
that I think we have
a good relationship,
but I won't do that again.
我不会再那么笨了
I agree.
我同意
Hey, Harper.
哈珀
I agree, 100 percent.
我完全同意
所有人都会这样，伊森
Everybody does it, Ethan.
I'm sure they're over there
shitting on me right now,
我保证他们正在说我坏话
说我是婊子，或是配不上你之类的
saying I'm a bitch
or... you could do better.
Or whatever.
Ah!
Ah. Vieni, bella!
（意语）过来，美女
- Come to Papa.
- Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
到我的怀里吧
就是这样‥
What do you think, huh, baby?
I like it.
（意语）好漂亮
Bellissimo!
你喜欢吗？
但我不想买那件裙子，米亚
我想买下整间店
你知道我会先做什么吗？
开除那个婊子
Bitch, you're fired.
婊子，你可以走人了
再见，婊子
所以他怎么样？
他怎么样？
他很紧张，但他喜欢我
Hmm.
这周我都会当他女朋友
我跟他提到你
－不会吧　－没错
那间饭店找我们麻烦
他说会跟他们谈谈
反正他们不会再让我进去了
我都往那个人脸上泼了酒
Mia.
米亚
很痛
那我的名声怎么办？
你的名声怎么了？
走吧，我会把你介绍给他
You sure you're okay to walk?
你确定能走吗？
Maybe we should get a taxi, Dad.
或许我们该叫计程车，爸爸
She said it's only
at the end of the...
她说走到大道尽头就到了
Of the corso.
If I'm a cripple,
nobody told me.
没有人说我不能走路
Um, you guys, I gotta make
a quick call, all right?
我得打通电话
你们先走，我待会儿跟上
Uh, you wanna keep walking
and I'll just catch up?
Okay. Dad,
it's this way.
好，爸爸，往这里走
－好啦‥
－知道了
Cool.
Oh, Mr. Di Grasso.
狄格拉索先生，早安
- Good Morning.
- Hello.
Uh, I just wanted to inform you
我想告知你，我的两位好朋友‥
that my good friends here, um...
- Lucia.
露西亚‥
- Mia.
- And Mia.
－米亚
－还有米亚
They're my good friends.
她们是我的好朋友
- They are your good friends?
- Yeah.
她们是您的好友？
是的，她们这周会来找我
Okay. And they're gonna
be visiting me this week.
Uh, a couple of nights maybe,
not exactly sure.
或许几个晚上，不太确定
But it seems
like they're having trouble
但她们好像无法正常进饭店
getting into the hotel.
So if you could just make sure
所以希望你确保她们能正常出入
they get access,
that would be wonderful.
Yeah. Um,
好
I'm afraid I will need to add
their names on your room,
我可能得把她们登记在您的房间
as we only allow
our guests into the hotel.
因为只有房客能进入我们饭店
Oh.
Um, well, all right.
Let's do that then.
好，就这么办
Add both their names
to your room?
她们两位都要登记？
对
Sure.
Um, I'm afraid
there is a little issue
可能有个问题
because your room
was booked only for two guests.
因为您订房时只订了两位房客
And if you are three,
如果有三人就会有额外费用
this is going to be
an extra charge.
Really?
真的？
Sorry about that.
很不好意思
We'd also have to charge
for setting up the extra bed.
多一张床也会多收取费用
No, we don't need an extra bed.
我们不需要多一张床
Are you going to sleep
你们都要睡在同一张床上？
all in the same bed?
No... no.
不是的
They'll be coming and going.
You see, they're locals.
她们不会久留
她们是当地人，我在这里的朋友
They're my local friends.
Oh. They come and go. I see.
她们不会久留，原来如此
Okay, how about this?
Why don't you, uh, put Lucia
好，这样如何
把露西亚登记在我房间
on my room and add...
然后把‥
- Mia.
- Mia to my father's room?
－米亚
－米亚登记在我爸房间
So she will be sleeping
with your father.
所以她会与您父亲过夜
No.
不是的
她们俩都不会过夜
She's not staying anywhere.
They're just gonna be
visiting me
她们只会来拜访我
and I'm hoping
you're gonna let them in.
我希望你能让她们进来
It's not that complicated,
is it?
没有很复杂吧？
- It's not.
- No.
－没有
－那就对了
Okay.
好
Yes, I will add their names.
我会帮她们登记
- So we're good?
- Yes.
所以没问题了？
－是的
－谢谢你
- Thank you.
- We welcome them.
我们欢迎她们
Thank you.
欢迎你们
- Okay, um...
- Grazie.
（意语）谢谢‥
Grazie.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Uh, uh, yes. Okay. Listen.
－谢谢你‥
－好
听着
Please don't make me
regret this.
－拜托不要惹麻烦，好吗？
－不会的
- Okay?
- No. Yes.
Um, you charge some food,
买点吃的，喝点葡萄酒
charge a little vino,
but don't go crazy.
但不要太过分
No, no, no. We...
We will don't go crazy.
不会的，我们不会太过分
The other thing is,
I'm here with my father
还有，我是跟父亲和儿子来的
and my son, so I can't really
be seen with you.
所以别人不能看见
我跟你们一起，了解吗？
- You understand that?
- Yes, I understand.
了解
晚上见
I'll see you tonight.
- Bye.
再见‥
可以给我们房间钥匙吗？
好，但冷静点，这里是五星级饭店
要有点‥
你也算在商界打滚吧？
当初会建造饭店
就是要赚我们这种女生的钱
别傻了
- Grazie.
- Prego.
－（意语）谢谢
－（意语）不客气
Venice is unbelievable.
威尼斯非常棒
We love Venice.
我们很喜欢威尼斯
还有那里的饭店
And the hotels!
Cam really likes the Cipriani.
卡麦隆很喜欢奇普里亚尼饭店
- Love it.
- Because of the boat ride
－我很喜欢
－能搭船穿越潟湖到城里
through the lagoon into town.
太酷了，那才叫人生啊，亲爱的
So cool.
I mean, that's living, honey.
是的，但是‥
- That is living.
- It is, yes. But.
You have to go
你们必须去住安缦饭店，相信我
and you have to stay
at the Aman.
Trust me.
I cried when I saw the view
from our room.
我看到窗外的景色时都哭了
- Hmm.
- And a princess lives there.
还有公主住在那里
It's somebody's house!
是别人的家
It's wild, though.
These European aristocrats,
但夸张的是，那些欧洲贵族没什么钱
- they have no money.
- Yeah.
－对
－真的
Like, I shit you not.
They have all these palazzos,
他们有很多宫殿，但没有现金
- and they got no cash.
- Uh-huh.
And they're so rude.
而且他们很无礼
Oh, my God, are they rude.
真的超级无礼
- Yeah.
- We could buy their palazzo,
我们都能买下他们的宫殿
他们还把我们当成‥
and they'd treat us like we're,
you know...
- Like bugs.
- Yeah.
虫子，恶心的虫子
- Like disgusting bugs.
- Yeah.
对
- That's funny.
- Yeah.
－真好笑
－是啊
Okay, so, you didn't go
to Venice on your honeymoon.
所以你们没去威尼斯度蜜月
- Where did you go?
- Yeah.
－你们是去哪里？
－对啊
We went to Puerto Rico.
我们是去波多黎各
Oh!
哈珀一半的家人都在那里
Harper has, like,
half her family out there, so...
That's right. Yeah, of course.
对，我记得你有一半波多黎各血统
I remember
you're half Puerto Rican.
- Yeah.
对
How is Puerto Rico?
波多黎各怎么样？
－很棒
－很漂亮
- It's awesome.
- Beautiful.
Yeah? That's cool.
是吗？
真有趣
- We should... we should go.
- Yes.
－我们该去看看
－没错
- I mean, we should totally go.
- Mm-hmm.
It's never really been
on our radar.
我们从没想过
- But we should check it out if you guys...
- No. Yeah.
－但我们也该去看看
－是啊
- Say it's great. Yeah.
- Yeah, you should.
And it's, um,
it's a part of America,
它属于美国，但不是一个州
- but it's not a s... state.
- Right.
－对
－因为它是‥
'Cause it's, um...
- It's a territory.
- Yes!
－自治邦
－没错
- Exactly. It's a territory. Duh.
- Territory.
自治邦‥
You should go.
If you ever wanna go,
你们该去看看，如果你们要去
you could stay with my family
in San Juan.
可以跟我在圣胡安的家人住
Yeah, we would love that.
那就太好了
太棒了
That's so nice.
米亚，你好漂亮
你也是
是不是花太多了？
不会，他是有钱人
稍等
稍等，我需要签名
１４８号房，露西亚格列柯
我们说了不行
为什么要帮她租伟士牌？
－她签免责声明了吗　－我会吐的
I'm gonna get sick.
You know what?
You need to be in the photo.
你应该要入镜
- No, I don't.
- You do.
－我不用
－你也要入镜
Yeah, get in the photo. I don't need
to be in the picture. Let's just go.
－我们赶快出发吧
－你从不会穿成这样
You're never
in a cute little suit like that,
你平常只穿着内裤
you're always in your underwear.
- Hey.
- Yes?
－怎么了？
－你好
- Hello.
- Hi.
Yeah, could you take
a photo of us...
可以帮我们拍张照吗？
- Yes.
- on the Vespa?
－好
－我们会坐在伟士牌上
- For sure.
- Thank you.
当然可以
您穿得好粉
- You look so pink.
- Here.
－给你
－猜猜我是谁
Guess who I am?
- Uh...
- Watch, watch.
看好喔
Peppa Pig.
佩佩猪
I'm Monica Vitti.
我是莫妮卡维蒂
Monica Vitti's dead, but yes.
莫妮卡维蒂去世了
但是的确很像
Oh, wait. Wait.
One more with my mouth shut.
等等，再拍张闭着嘴的
- Very sexy. Brava.
- Mm.
很性感，真棒
Brava, Monica.
很棒，莫妮卡
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
－谢谢你
－不客气
Uh...
Are you sure
you don't need a car?
你确定不开车吗？
No, this is...
This is the Italian dream.
不用，这是梦幻意大利之旅
Yes, but, uh,
the road can be really tricky.
没错，但是‥
路况可能不太好
Yeah, but we... And you
know, Sicilian drivers...
是啊
而且西西里人开车‥
Is this the, uh,
normal size of a Vespa?
这是正常大小的伟士牌吗？
Yes. Vespa, normal size. Yes.
是的，正常大小
Uh-oh.
- All right.
- Oh, my God.
－出发
－天啊
Oh.
Oh, shit.
是水上摩托车
- Jet skis?
- Oh.
Oh, that's awesome.
We gotta do that, huh?
太酷了，我们一定要骑
Daph, come on,
take them down the coast?
达芙妮，我们沿着海岸骑如何？
Ooh. No thanks.
不用了
Oh.
E-man, what about you?
You'd be up for that?
伊老大呢，你想骑吗？
I don't know, maybe.
不知道，或许吧
Yeah, I guess.
好吧
You gotta have motor skills
for something like that.
身体要够协调才能驾驭那种东西
What's that supposed to mean?
什么意思？
I'm kidding, man,
I'm kidding. So...
我开玩笑的
那么‥
Little elephant in the room,
how do you guys like being rich?
有件事我一直想问
有钱的感觉如何？
- Oh, Cameron. God.
- What? Come on.
－卡麦隆，天啊
－怎么了？
Major windfall, right?
意外发了大财，对吧？
I mean, nothing much
has changed, to be honest.
说实话，没什么不同
Nice to be able to help people,
I guess.
－能帮助别人是还不错
－是啊
- Yeah. Right.
- Yeah.
And helping Harper's parents,
my sister.
帮助哈珀父母，我妹
Yeah, we're not
very materialistic, so it's...
我们不太需要物质享受，所以‥
- Oh, yeah?
- Harper's thinking
是吗？
哈珀在考虑设立一个基金会
of starting
a little foundation, actually.
Nice.
真棒
Yeah, I'm working
with the Hispanic Federation.
我在跟西语裔基金会合作
Great.
太棒了
Yeah, we're involved
in a lot of charities.
我们也参与很多慈善活动，对吧？
- Right, Daph?
- Mm-hmm.
You know, sometimes
if I've had too much to drink,
有时如果我喝太多
I wake up the next day
and I realize
隔天醒来会发现自己花了很多钱
- I've spent a lot of money.
- Yeah.
－对
－非常多钱
- Like, a lot of money.
- Like, all the money.
几乎全都花光了
If I have had wine
如果我喝了酒，滑手机
and I'm scrolling
and I see anything
只要看到缺乏关爱的婴儿孩童
with like neglected children
or babies or abused animals,
或是受虐的动物
我就会很难受
it's like, I can't.
I mean, people
are just so fucked up.
有些人真的很糟糕
- Yeah.
－是啊
－没错
Yeah, we're not
just materialistic pigs.
我们不是物质主义的蠢蛋
Despite what you might think.
虽然你或许是这么想的
I don't... I don't think that.
我不是这么想的
No, I...
没有，我‥
I don't think that.
我没有这么想
I'm gonna go for a swim.
我要去游泳
Have fun.
祝你游得开心
Something I said?
我说错话了吗？
I'm gonna go for a swim.
我去游泳
Oh, my God.
What a view.
好棒的景色
I think I'll sit down.
我得坐一下
Oh.
- Ah!
- You okay, Bert?
你还好吗，伯特？
- Want some of my water?
- Oh.
要喝点水吗？
It was a long walk, Dad.
You did great.
走了很远，爸爸，你很厉害
Mm.
That is lava, it's erupting.
那里有岩浆，火山在活动
Thank you, Cara.
谢谢你，卡拉
Portia, Nonno.
她叫波蒂亚
- Her name's Portia.
- Cara's my granddaughter.
卡拉是我孙女
- Hmm.
- Who should be here.
她原本也该来的
她为什么没来？
Why isn't she here?
Dad, how many times
do we have to go over this?
爸爸，你要说几次？
Well, she's my granddaughter
and I wanted her here.
她是我孙女，我希望她来
It hurts my feelings.
我很伤心
Well, you can tell her
your feelings
你下次见到她可以告诉她
next time you see her.
What did you do anyway?
你到底做了什么？
What is so bad that you did?
有什么事能糟糕成这样？
- Fuck.
- Nonno, come on.
－可恶
－爷爷，不要这样
Fine.
好吧
We're in Sicily.
Isn't this incredible?
我们在西西里，真不可思议
It... it's so old.
这里历史非常悠久
It is pretty crazy
to wrap your head around.
想想的确挺不可思议的
You know, Hades raped Persephone
right here in Sicily.
是的
黑帝斯在这里侵犯了波瑟芬妮
She was picking flowers
and he burst through the earth
她当时在采花
他突然从地底出现并侵犯了她
- and he raped her.
- Okay, Nonno.
够了，爷爷
Well, that's what happened.
He raped her.
事实就是这样，他侵犯了她
Then, he dragged her down
to the underworld.
接着把她拖进了冥界
Hmm. I didn't know that.
我不知道这些
Demeter forgave Hades,
and he raped her daughter!
狄蜜特都原谅了侵犯自己女儿的人
I mean, whatever you've done
can't be as bad as that.
你做的事不可能会这么糟
As Hades. And the raping.
不会跟黑帝斯侵犯她一样糟吧
Had to do it. Sorry.
我没忍住，抱歉
I thought you were a shark.
我以为是鲨鱼
Hey, sorry about before,
you know?
刚才很抱歉
I didn't mean
to make you feel uncomfortable,
我不是故意要让你不舒服
I just...
I feel like I keep saying
the wrong thing, you know?
我好像一直说错话
你好像不喜欢我
I feel like you don't like me.
我喜欢你，怎么了吗？
I like you. What?
Well, it's just important,
I want you to like us.
这很重要，我希望你喜欢我们
I want you to like me.
我希望你喜欢我
I like you both.
我喜欢你们俩
Yeah. Definitely.
真的
Good.
好
All right, I'll leave you to it.
那我就不打扰你了
Tanya.
－谭雅
－我的天啊
Oh, my God.
Release your grip a little bit.
抱小力一点
Tanya.
谭雅，我吸不到气
- Yeah?
- I can't breathe.
We're in like...
In a James Bond movie.
我们好像在演００７系列电影
You're gonna make us crash.
你会害我们摔车
Lucia.
露西亚，你看起来很有钱
谢谢你，亲爱的
－也很性感　－你也是
怎么了，米亚？
那是你的男朋友
真大胆
停战‥
我好像有点醉
我也是
Tanya, what are you doing?
谭雅，你在做什么？
我吃到虫子
I got a bug.
Careful.
It's fluttering around in there.
翅膀在动，不知道怎么进去的
You're gonna make us crash.
Be careful. Be careful!
你会害我们摔车
小心点‥谭雅
Tanya!
Tanya. Hold on.
谭雅
抓好
－米亚　－干嘛？
我们今晚必须来次三人行
因为你现在欠他了
露西亚，我也想，但问题是‥
－什么？　－你也在旁边
笨蛋
Oh!
我们得快点，答应我，好吗？
－好　－来吧
Okay.
我们得把东西藏好才不会被偷
谁会偷？
我太喜欢我的衣服了
这是我新买的，米亚
瞧瞧有多漂亮
请问房号
Um...
１４８号
- Grazie.
- Di niente.
（意语）谢谢
Mm.
我很快就回来
（意语）你好
Ciao.
我不气你，所以也别气我，好吗？
Mm-hmm.
我得说清楚
我不是妓女
我是歌手
不相信？
那我唱给你听
Uh...
一首就好
不必了
这里又没人，一首就好
我保证你会喜欢的
快点，一首而已
The moon belongs
＂月亮属于每一个人＂
To everyone
The best things in life Are free
＂生命中最美好的事物都是无价的＂
The stars belong to everyone
＂星空属于每一个人＂
They gleam there for you
And for me
＂为了你我而闪烁＂
The flowers in Spring
＂春天的花朵＂
The robins that sing
＂歌唱着的知更鸟＂
＂闪耀着的阳光＂
Sunbeams that shine
They're yours, they're mine
＂它们属于你，属于我＂
And love can come To everyone
＂爱情会找上每一个人＂
The best things in life Are free
＂生命中最美好的事物都是无价的＂
＂生命中最美好的事物＂
The best
Things in life
Are
＂都是无价的＂
Free
（意语）唱得好，米亚
Brava! Brava, Mia!
Bravissima!
（意语）太棒了
你唱得真棒
来庆祝一下，再两杯，谢谢
－是吗？
－对，我一直都想
餐厅在这里
I think
the restaurant's... here.
- This is the spot.
- Right here.
Ciao.
（意语）你好
- I can get that for you.
- Thanks.
我帮你拉椅子
谢谢
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
What?
怎么了？
Do you wanna leave?
你想离开这里吗？
Should we go?
要走吗？
Oh, there, let me do it.
There we are. There it is.
我帮你脱
好了
Okay, thank you.
谢谢你
Okay.
好
I have to eat.
You know, like I...
我还是得吃饭，我‥
- Yeah.
- I don't know what she... Ugh.
－是啊
－我不知道她‥
- Okay.
- Yeah.
－但我们就当作没事吧
－好
Um, but we can just ignore it.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- Yeah. Maybe we could
或许我们可以喝杯酒
just get a glass of wine, just...
好，喝一杯吧
Yeah, let's get a drink.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Why isn't she responding to me?
It's not like my mom.
她为什么没回复我？
我妈妈不会这样
Come on, babe. They're...
They're fine, all right?
拜托，宝贝，他们没事的
Relax. Put your phone down.
Drink your wine.
放轻松，手机放一边
－喝点酒
－你说得对，好
You're right. Okay.
They're fine.
他们没事的
How about you guys?
Do you wanna have kids?
你们呢？
你们想要小孩吗？
Uh...
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
想‥
我们有一阵子不太确定
- We weren't sure for a while.
- Yeah. We've debated it a lot.
我们争论了很多次
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
让一个孩子来到现今的世界
Yeah, you know, just bringing
a kid into the world right now,
这么混乱的世界
everything going on...
Never mind.
算了
But we decided that we want to,
so we've been trying.
但我们最后决定要，所以在努力
- Cool.
- Not that hard.
－真棒
－没有很努力
How long have you been trying?
你们试多久了？
Oh, I don't know. Not that long.
不知道，没有很久
Problem is I'm more
of a morning sex guy
问题是，我比较喜欢早上做
and Harper
is not a morning person.
但哈珀不喜欢早上做
- Hmm.
- She's a night person.
她比较喜欢晚上
But by then with work and stuff,
I'm always fried. So...
但我工作完晚上都很累，所以‥
Yeah, makes sense.
Yeah.
合理
What? Is that not right?
怎么，我说错了吗？
So what you're saying is,
you don't have sex.
所以你们不做爱
No, we have s...
We're good. We're...
不是的，我们没有问题
- Never have sex.
- We... we have sex.
－从不做爱？
－我们会
做得很开心
- Oh.
- No, the sex is amazing.
- Oh. Gotcha.
- Uh-huh.
只是还没怀孕而已
You know, just not gotten
pregnant yet, is all.
I think it's...
我觉得‥
hard to sync up sometimes,
you know?
有时两人很难在同一条线上
Yeah.
Especially with kids. I mean,
it just gets worse.
尤其是生小孩后，会更难
I love my kids
but it's, you know,
我爱我的小孩，但我觉得压力很大
it's very stressful for me.
Not for him, but for me.
他不觉得，只有我
What? You kidding me?
The last one almost killed me.
你在开玩笑吗？
我上次差点被吓死
Cameron,
it didn't almost kill you,
卡麦隆，差点死的是我
it almost killed me.
真是一场恶梦
Well,
it was a fucking nightmare.
Yeah, it was. I had to have
an emergency cesarean.
真的
我得进行紧急剖腹产手术
They induced me
and then suddenly
引产后，他们突然说婴儿没心跳
they couldn't find
the baby's heartbeat. So...
I walk into the room and then...
我走进手术室，看到‥
Daphne's guts are all over
the table, you know?
达芙妮的内脏摊在手术台上
And... and they're looking
for the baby,
医生找婴儿的样子
就像达芙妮在翻包包找东西
like Daphne looks for something
in her fucking purse and...
- Her face.
- The...
她的脸
look on her face.
她的表情
It's in those moments
you realize just how much
这种时候会意识到自己多爱一个人
you love somebody, you know?
我爱你
I love you. Sweet baby.
宝贝
- Anyway.
- Yeah, anyway.
－总之
－对，总之
－换个话题
－手术成功了
- Change the subject.
- Everything turned out great.
Yeah.
Your mistake was being sloppy.
你错在太马虎
What are we talking about?
你在说什么？
That's what's unforgivable.
这才是无法饶恕的
A man does what he has to do.
男人难免会做些事
But you keep it tight.
If you're sloppy,
但必须处理干净
要是马虎了，就是在羞辱她
it's like you're rubbing
her face in it. Bad form.
这可不能接受
多谢指教
Thanks for the tip.
You know, I don't think
你自己外遇时
你其实也没多谨慎
you were as discreet
as you think you were
regarding your own affairs.
Affairs. They weren't affairs,
they were nothing.
那不叫外遇，没什么大不了的
They were peccadilloes.
那只是小小的错误
Peccadilloes?
小小的错误？
Fix it.
想办法处理好
I don't know if I can.
我不确定是否能做到
Of course you can.
Just get your act together.
当然能做到
只要你振作起来
My dad, uh, has cheated
on my mom a lot.
我爸外遇很多次
Mm-hmm.
And he just got caught again.
最近又被抓到
Yikes for him.
他惨了
Yeah. But that's why my mom
and sister aren't here.
是啊，所以我妈和妹妹才没来
They're really pissed.
她们很生气
你气吗？
Are you pissed?
Um...
yeah.
会啊
But I'm the peacemaker, so...
但我是和事佬，所以‥
Oh.
So you're like
the nice one in the family.
所以你是家里比较和善的那个人
That's sweet.
你人真好
Are you like that in, um,
relationships and stuff?
你谈恋爱也是那样吗？
Like, are you the "nice guy"?
是比较和善的那个？
Yeah. I try to be. Um...
我会尽量
Girls always complain
that guys aren't nice,
女生总是抱怨男生坏
but then if they find
a nice guy,
但又不太喜欢人很好的男生
they're not always interested.
- Hmm.
- But...
但是‥
I just don't wanna be
like my dad.
我只是不想变得像我爸
You know?
你懂吗？
I... I refuse to have
a bad relationship with women.
我不想搞砸跟女人的关系
Yeah.
我懂
I just wanna have fun.
我只是想找乐子
Hmm.
我只是想感觉到‥
Like, I just wanna...
I don't know, feel, like,
fulfilled and have an adventure,
满足
踏上冒险
and, like,
I'm sick of fucking TikTok
我受够了该死的短影音
and... and Bumble,
and just... screens and apps
交友软体
整天滑手机，窝在家看影集
and sitting there
binging Netflix.
And I just... I just wanna,
like, live.
我只是想‥
我很想好好过我的人生
I just wanna live my life,
so badly.
I just feel like I just wanna
meet someone who's like,
我希望能遇到‥
you know, totally ignorant of...
完全不晓得当前论述的人
the discourse.
You know?
你是说住在洞穴里的人
Right. Right. Like...
Like someone
who lives in a cave.
Like a caveman.
跟原始人一样的人
Yeah, uh, yeah, I would date
a caveman at this point. Yeah.
对，现在要我跟原始人交往也行
I mean...
I think you could aim higher.
我觉得你可以提高标准
Honestly, I think you can
do better than a caveman.
说真的，你能找到比原始人更好的人
I think I just need to...
我觉得我只是需要‥
I don't know, like, up my meds
or something.
再多吃点药之类的
Anyways, um, what about you?
总之，那你呢？
What kind of girl or person
do you wanna, you know,
你希望跟怎样的女生或对象交往？
be in a relationship with
or see yourself with or...
Um...
I seem to be attracted
to pretty...
我好像都会喜欢上‥
受过伤的人
wounded birds.
Got my pasta vongole
with giant clams.
吃了有大蛤蜊的意大利面
And then a Vespa ride with you.
跟你骑伟士牌兜风
You're wearing the shirt
that I gave you.
你穿着我给你的衣服
You made my Italian dream
come true.
你圆了我的意大利梦
非常谢谢你
Thank you very much.
I feel like Monica Vitti.
I really do.
我觉得自己就像莫妮卡维蒂
I wanted you to have
a perfect day.
我希望你先渡过完美的一天
Before I told you the news.
再告诉你一件事
什么事？
What news?
I have to fly
to Denver tomorrow.
我明天得飞去丹佛
What?
什么？
It's just for like two,
three days.
只会去两，三天
We're only here for a week. Why?
我们只来这里一周，为什么？
They're trying to slash
our budget.
他们想砍我们的预算
I have to go out there
and have a showdown
我得去跟那些浑蛋一决雌雄
with these fuckers,
and it's just bad timing.
不巧的是明天就得去
Yeah. But, I mean,
couldn't someone else do it?
不能让别人去吗？
You're on vacation.
你在度假
Yeah. You insisted
that we come to Sicily
你坚持要来西西里共度浪漫的一周
and have this romantic week.
And then you... you freaked out
你看到我和波蒂亚时很生气
when I showed up with Portia.
But thank God,
she's here, you know,
但还好她来了
否则我就要孤单一人了
because otherwise I'd be...
I'd be entirely alone.
Tanya, I didn't want this.
谭雅，我也不想这样
Well, can't you just quit
那就辞掉土地管理局什么的烂工作
the Bureau of Land Management
bullshit, whatever it is?
I can't quit.
I can't afford to quit.
我不能辞职
你逼我签了婚前协议书
You made me sign a prenup.
What if we don't work out?
如果我们分开了
我又没工作该怎么办？
If we don't work out,
what am I supposed to do
without a job?
- We're gonna work out, Greg.
- How do I know?
我们不会分开的
我怎么知道？
You change your mind
about everything constantly.
不管什么事你都这样阴晴不定
You... you...
You drop your friends.
你会跟朋友绝交
You fire people on a dime.
突然开除员工
I mean, you've been through...
你换了几个助理了？
How many fucking assistants
have you been through?
You just discard people.
你会随便把人丢掉
- You hate me, don't you?
- Shut up. I do not.
你恨我，对吧？
－别这样，我不恨你
－你恨我
- No, you do.
- No, I don't.
－我不恨你
－你就是恨我
No, I think you do.
You know what?
I'm paying attention.
告诉你
我看得很清楚
- Stop. I get it.
- I am paying attention.
－别这样
－我看得很清楚
－我能理解
－我看得出你讨厌我
- I can tell you don't like me.
- It's two days.
我只会去两天
可以不要又大吵吗？
Let's not just go into one
of these big dramas again, okay?
Fuck it, you're not coming back
in two days. You know what?
算了，你两天后也不会回来
你是个满嘴谎言的人
You're just...
You're a full-of-shit man.
You're very insincere.
And I can just tell.
你非常不真诚
我看得出来，你从不会直视我
You know what? You never look me
in the eye, ever.
Guess what? I'm telling you
in your eye,
看好了
我现在看着你的眼睛告诉你
you're a piece of shit.
你是个王八蛋
I hate you.
我恨你
Come on, Tanya. Tanya!
拜托你，谭雅
谭雅
It's always something with them.
他们总是有问题吵
- Uh, this is my room.
- Oh.
我的房间到了
Uh... Listen.
听我说
Please don't repeat
any of the shit that I told you
拜托不要
把我老板和她老公的事说出去
about my boss
and her husband and stuff,
因为我签了保密协议
because I actually
did sign an NDA
and I'm kinda paranoid about it.
我挺焦虑的
Yeah, I'm gonna tell
everyone I know.
我会告诉所有认识的人
No, I'm just kidding.
开玩笑的，我当然不会说出去
I... Yeah, of course,
I would never do that.
如果她告我会很可笑
Yeah, it'd be ridiculous
if she actually sued me,
'cause all I have is my laptop
因为我只有一台笔电
and she has
half a billion dollars.
而她有五亿元
Her dad was this big,
like, shipping magnate guy
她爸是运输业的巨头
and owned like half
of San Francisco.
旧金山有一半都是他的
And... and I don't think
he molested her,
他应该没有侵犯她
but he was definitely
very pervy and inappropriate
但他绝对是个变态，行为龌龊
and then it was kind of sad.
挺可怜的，他后来自杀了
He actually ended up
committing suicide and...
and I'm not supposed to be
telling you that either.
我也不该告诉你这些的
Um...
can I kiss you?
我可以亲你吗？
Oh. Um...
sure.
可以
好
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Um, I guess...
那么‥
let's hang out tomorrow.
明天再见吧
好
Okay.
Um, good night. Yeah. I had fun.
晚安
我玩得很开心
开心，太好了
Fun. Great. Okay.
Good night.
晚安
I'm sorry.
对不起
- For what?
- For being a shrew.
干嘛对不起？
我总是在抱怨
I feel like I'm ruining
this trip for everybody.
我觉得我毁了大家的兴致
- No, you're not.
- I just...
你没有
我不知道在不满什么，感觉像‥
I don't know what my problem is.
I just feel like...
I feel like we're LARPing
as rich people.
我们在假装自己是有钱人
We're not LARPing.
How... how are we LARPing?
才没有，为什么是在假装？
And I don't know, I guess,
I just don't want him
不知道，我只是不希望你被他影响
rubbing off on you.
You know, and I don't like
the way he alpha dogs you.
－我也讨厌他老是气势压着你
－他没有
He doesn't alpha dog me.
I mean, he kind of used to,
I guess,
以前或许会，但是‥
but... it's different now.
现在不同了
Oh, my God,
is that why we're here?
天啊，所以我们才来这里吗？
So you can rub your success
in his face?
你想在他面前炫耀一番？
No.
不是
So you can finally win
the arm wrestling contest.
你才能比腕力赢过他？
我们没有在比赛
No. There is no contest.
Well, whatever. From now on,
I am going to be...
随便
我接下来会当个开心果
so fun. Okay?
- I promise.
- Okay.
我保证
好
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
Do you wanna suck on my tits
or jerk off on my face
你想吸我胸部或是在我脸上自慰吗？
or something? Fuck around?
来点有趣的？
I'm kinda beat.
我有点累了
Yeah, okay.
好
Ugh. She sucks.
她真无趣
Why would he marry her?
他为什么会娶她？
- She's pretty.
- Yeah, I guess.
她很漂亮
或许吧
But she's such a pill.
但她很讨人厌
You know, I think some women
cut off their husband's balls
有些女人会夺走男人的卵蛋
然后纳闷自己为何不喜欢他了
and then they wonder
why they're not attracted
to them anymore.
Yeah. Don't you cut
my balls off, baby.
是啊
不准夺走我的卵蛋，宝贝
不会的
I won't.
That's all I got, sugarplum.
我只剩这个了，宝贝
- But you know what?
- What?
但你知道吗？
知道什么？
- If I wanted to...
- Uh-huh.
如果我想
I could.
我是做得到的
Buonasera!
（意语）你好
Hello.
你好
We had a great day.
我们今天很开心
We drank by the pool,
we had dinner,
在泳池边喝酒，吃晚餐
and I just wanted to thank you.
我想谢谢你
You're very welcome.
不客气
Um, but listen...
但听我说‥
I'm having like
a guilty conscience
我现在有种愧疚感
kind of feeling, you know.
感觉不太好
I'm... I'm just not feeling great
about this. Uh, you're lovely.
你很棒
You don't want me to come in?
你不希望我进去？
Oh, I really do.
You have no idea.
我非常希望
我有性成瘾和冲动控制的问题
I have a problem
with sexual addiction
and compulsion.
It's a... it's a real issue.
And, uh...
很严重
I... I really need
to get a handle on it,
我必须赶快学会控制
like, quickly, if I'm gonna turn
my situation around.
才能改变我的处境
You understand?
你懂吗？
I have my friend here,
and she wants to thank you, too.
我带了朋友来，她也想谢谢你
- Ciao.
- Hi.
－（意语）你好
－你好
谢谢你帮我出比基尼的钱
Thank you for my bikini.
You're welcome.
不客气
Sure you don't want us
to come in?
确定不希望我们进去吗？
Jeez.
You're making this very hard.
我很为难
Please.
拜托啦
Oh, Lord.
天啊
- Mm.
- Um...
（意语）如果我被闪电击中‥
米凯莱
Michele...
西西里的女人比枪还危险
Do you like vodka?
Mia, get the vodka.
Mm-hmm.
Greg?
葛瑞格？
Yeah, she's clueless as usual.
她还是没发现
I'll be home tomorrow,
give you a call when I get in.
我明天就回去，到家后打给你
All right, yeah, I love you too.
我也爱你
And I look forward to it.
我很期待
待续
谢谢观赏